roblav96@gmail.com



401-203-3195



New York, NY



Altruistic, ego-free, humble, open-minded



Leader, openly criticize, will take charge



"If you want to go far, go

Eager to learn, more eager



Public seminar speaker & event attendee



+2,000 GitHub contributions yearly



TypeScript



Node.js

to teach

together"





Vue.js React



RxJS



Redis



MongoDB



Amazon Web Services



Terminal / Bash

Google Analytics



Ubuntu



NativeScript



Sublime Text

Robert Laverty

Full-Stack Software Engineer





/roblav96

README.md

I'm a Problem Solver. That statement can easily be validated by the numerous projects I've created from the ground up. Every project was developed because of a problem I had experienced myself. I've taken them from an idea, all the way to a minimum viable product and talking to investors. Throughout these endeavors I've learned how to efficiently identify a problem, produce a solution based on meaningful metrics, analytics, and A/B tests, market and sell the product, then scale to a larger audience. I want to put my extraordinary skill-sets to good use at your company and work with a team of your best innovators. Please don't hesitate to contact me if you have any questions. Thank you!

Experience



<u>LeverEdge</u> - Lead Software Engineer

Playwright/Puppeteer, then pandemic...

Feb 2020 - Apr 2020

May 2019 - Oct 2019

















Upgraded frontend to use Nuxt.js, created a LinkedIn scraper with headless

<u>DocHub</u> - Lead Software Engineer Scaled product, integrated analytics/metrics, upgraded frontend to use TypeScript







Futon Media - Creator

Sep 2018 - Dec 2019















Designed, developed, and deployed customer-facing 'Kava Switch' blockchain platform



Robinhood Tools - Creator

Dec 2016 - Aug 2018

Sep 2018 - Apr 2019

















Sep 2016 - Aug 2017

Sep 2015 - Dec 2015

Sep 2012 - Aug 2015

Designed, developed, and deployed native mobile platform on iOS & Android using NativeScript

Helped develop scanner reporting front-end in an agile environment using scrum methodologies













EMC Corporation - Full-Stack Software Engineer

Boustris & Sons - Head of Information Technology

<u>GetHuman</u> - Senior Full-Stack Software Engineer





Developed their fire alarm testing and inspection application & troubleshoot repair installed





Facepunch Studios - Game Developer

networked IT systems in commercial buildings

Jul 2007 - Aug 2009

Developed games on Steam using the Lua programming language

Education



Google Primer - Grow With Google Program

Insights from trusted industry experts insights from trusted industry experts into jargon-free interactive lessons featuring practical next steps for reaching your business or career goals



<u>University of Rhode Island</u> - Computer Science Voluntarily resigned due to financial constraints

Sep 2009 - June 2010